so yesterday I reported on the
experiment where scientists were able to
take the brains out of the skulls of the
deceased and revive them in a vat hours
later and initially I thought that was
one of my Tamer incomprehensible horror
series is but I realized today
they slaughtered these pigs removed
their brains from their bodies revived
them in a vat long after their bodies
had been sent down the processing line
for bacon they could have already been
packaged by the time their brains came
back online
in a vat now sitting there with no
stimuli locked in and picked their very
intelligent creatures I can understand
why this was a controversy about the
ethics of the experiment
it also means that we are a lot closer
to being able to do a brain transplant
in our lifetimes combined with the
technology of the neural regenerative
brain organoids which can be implanted
into somebody's brain and come online we
should be able to heal neural damage
pretty quickly it's great for people
with spinal injuries but brain
transplants
unfortunately the people who might have
access to things like brain transplants
are not the kind of people we want to
live forever
what do you think